Mohd Yasin Munshi

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India



mohdyasinn6@gmail.com



8421243495



linkedin.com/in/mohdyasinn

Summary

About Me:

Name: Muhammed Yasin Abdul Gafoor Munshi Date of Birth: 04/03/2004 (19 Years old)

Currently Pursuing in 2nd Year Bachelor of Engineering in Electronics & Computer Science

I am a self-taught Graphic Designer & Video Editor and UI/UX Designer

Freelancing & Working for Esports Organizations based out of India remotely for 1-2 Years

And I have 1-year experience of working with a Creative Agency https://tragik.gg/

Experience



Freelance Designer

Jan 2023 - Present (9 months)



Chasmac Gaming

Nov 2021 - Jan 2022 (3 months)

Senior Graphic Designer & Video Editor

Claxon Tournaments Pte. Ltd.

Jun 2020 - Jan 2022 (1 year 8 months)



M Director Of Graphic Design

Tragik Design LLC

Jan 2021 - Sep 2021 (9 months)



Graphic Designer

SGH—Esports Streaming Network

Nov 2020 - Jul 2021 (9 months)

Education



University of Mumbai



Anjuman-I-Islam's Kalsekar Technical Campus

Bachelor of Engineering - University of Mumbai - Electronics & Computer Science, Engineering

Anjuman-I-Islam's Abdul Razzaq Kalsekar Polytechnic
High School Diploma, Electronics & Telecommunication Engineering

Jul 2019 - Jul 2022

Licenses & Certifications

- The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp Udemy UC-ef8e8010-2a92-46d0-ab98-68710fbf10b1
- **G** Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design Google Career Certificates
- G Design a User Experience for Social Good & Prepare for Jobs Google Career Certificates
- **G** Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity Prototypes Google Career Certificates
- Start the UX Design Process: Empathize, Define, and Ideate Google Career Certificates
- Conduct UX Research and Test Early Concepts Google Career Certificates
- Create High-Fidelity Designs and Prototypes in Figma Google Career Certificates
- **G** Responsive Web Design in Adobe XD Google Career Certificates
- Google UX Design Certificate Coursera

Skills

Usabilit • Adobe XD • mockup • Usability Testing • UX Design Job • UX Reserch • Prototype • User Experience Design (UED) • UI Design • User Interface Prototyping